Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Pierre Moerlen's Gong - Time is the key, 1979; SR-23400; Pierre Moerlen's Gong (Box 389)
          Catalog # AB 4255; A-side Matrix # T1 AB-4255-SACT-1
        - Pig Force - Afrika pig, 1996; SR-23401; Pig Force (Box 389)
          Catalog # 12BRW 343; A-side Matrix # 12 BRW 343-A+ MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE
        - Pigbag - The big bean, 1982; SR-23402; Pigbag (Box 389)
          Catalog # 12" Y USA 5; A-side Matrix # 12"-Y-USA-5-A
          Y America
        - Pike, Dave - Mathar - the original Indian vibes, 1997; SR-23404; Pike, Dave; Dave Pike Set (Box 389)
          Catalog # OUT9X; A-side Matrix # SIMON-THE EXCHANGE OUT 9-A2
          Outcaste Records
        - Pike, Dave - Mathar - the original Indian vibes, 1997; SR-23405; Pike, Dave; Dave Pike Set (Box 389)
        - Pills - Rock me (remix dirty beatniks), 1998; SR-23406; Pills (Box 389)
          Catalog # 568 971-1; A-side Matrix # DFI-98-4 568971-1 A MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE
        - Pink Floyd - A momentary lapse of reason, 1987; SR-23407; Pink Floyd (Box 389)
          Catalog # EMD 1003; A-side Matrix # EMD 1003-A3 DMM PRECISION EMD 1003 A-3U-1-2
          EMI
        - Pink Lady - Kiss in the dark, 1979; SR-25089; Pink Lady (Box 389)
          Catalog # AS-11413; A-side Matrix # ASS-11413 A SP 1-5
        - Pink Project - Split, 1983; SR-23408; Pink Project (Box 389)
          Catalog # 66070; A-side Matrix # 66070 A
          Carrere
        - Pink Project - B. Project, 1983; SR-23409; Pink Project (Box 389)
          Catalog # 8275; A-side Matrix # 8275 A
        - Pink Project - Domino (disc one), 1982; SR-23410; Pink Project (Box 389)
          In same jacket as # SR-23411; SR-23412. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 67956; A-side Matrix # 67956 A
        - Pink Project - Domino (disc one), 1982; SR-23411; Pink Project (Box 389)
          In same jacket as # SR-23410; SR-23412. Double album.
        - Pink Project - Domino (disc two), 1982; SR-23412; Pink Project (Box 389)
          In same jacket as # SR-23410; SR-23411. Double album.
          Catalog # 67956; A-side Matrix # 67956 C
        - Pink Rythm - Can't get enough of your love, 1985; SR-23413; Pink Rythm; Rocca, John (Box 389)
          Catalog # MET 240; A-side Matrix # "THIS ONE IS HOT AND FRESH" 240-A
          Metropolis Records
        - Pinky - Looking for a love, 1991; SR-23414; Pinky (Box 389)
          Catalog # RUFF 12; A-side Matrix # RUFF12A1 MIKE'S-THE EXCHANGE
          1st Bass
        - Pinto, Kathi - Too many nights, 1982; SR-23415; Pinto, Kathi (Box 389)
          Catalog # SR 1001; A-side Matrix # SR 1001-A12 PRC-C1-1-1
          Simon Records
          Long Beach, California
        - Pioneers - We funk this party out, 1996; SR-23416; Pioneers (Box 389)
          Catalog # EDL 4655-6; A-side Matrix # 0046556EDL A1 MK
          IDE International Design
        - Pipedream - Quicksand, 1983; SR-23417; Pipedream (Box 390)
          Catalog # 4W9-04270; A-side Matrix # "DEEPER" CUT FROM JOSÉ D KANDOR P 4W-9-04270-AS
          Zoo York Recordz
        - Piscopo, Joe - Honeymooners rap, 1985; SR-23418; Piscopo, Joe; Murphy, Eddie (Box 390)
          Catalog # 44-05224; A-side Matrix # P-AP XXS 174393-2A
        - Piscopo, Tullio De - Andamento lento (club mix), 1988; SR-23419; Piscopo, Tullio De (Box 390)
          Catalog # 14 2025176; A-side Matrix # 2025176-A 9-3-88 IX DE-PISCOPO
          Costa Est
        - Pish Posh - Indoor storm (disc one), 2000; SR-23420; Pish Posh (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23421. Double album.
          Catalog # RKT-1182; A-side Matrix # RKT-1182A
          Rawkuts
        - Pish Posh - Indoor storm (disc two), 2000; SR-23421; Pish Posh (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23420. Double album.
          Catalog # RKT-1182; A-side Matrix # RKT-1182C
        - Pismo - The game, 2001; SR-23422; Pismo (Box 390)
          Catalog # SR 0003; A-side Matrix # 7058-SR003-1CA1 S 46901 RE1
          Shou Records
        - Pismo - The game, 2001; SR-23423; Pismo (Box 390)
        - Pistol - Rolling in my '64, 1994; SR-23424; Pistol (Box 390)
          Catalog # 88561-5531-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-5531-1 A F/W
          Ruthless Records
        - Pistol Pete - 1 mission 2 make u dance, 1997; SR-23425; Pistol Pete; DJ York (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23426. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BDS-957; A-side Matrix # BDS-957-A F/W
          New Break Records
        - Pistol Pete - 1 mission 2 make u dance, 1997; SR-23426; Pistol Pete; DJ York (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23425. 2 copies.
        - Pistol Pete - Rewind!, 2000; SR-23427; Pistol Pete (Box 390)
          Catalog # REWIND-0768; A-side Matrix # REWIND-0768-A
        - Pitbull - Down south; Playa haters, 2005; SR-23428; Pitbull; Duece Poppi; Cubo (Box 390)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # PITBULL DOWN SOUTH-A
          RudeBwoy Entertainment
        - Pitcho - District 1030, 2002; SR-23429; Pitcho (Box 390)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # PITCHO A
          360° Records
        - Pixies - Monkey gone to heaven, 1989; SR-23430; Pixies (Box 390)
          Catalog # 0-66707; A-side Matrix # STED-66707A-1
        - Pizarro - Mine forever mine, 1993; SR-23431; Pizarro; Blakely, Donna (Box 390)
          Catalog # RZZ-111; A-side Matrix # R22111LP-A
          Razz Enterprises, Inc.
        - P.J. Master - Dance kriminals, 1991; SR-23432; P.J. Master (Box 390)
          Catalog # DW 1921; A-side Matrix # DW 1921-A
        - Planet Patrol - I didn't know I loved you (till I saw you rock & roll), 1983; SR-23433; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          Catalog # TB 837; A-side Matrix # "IT'S HOT" TB-837-A
        - Planet Patrol - It wouldn't have made any difference, 1984; SR-23434; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          Catalog # TB 843; A-side Matrix # TB-843-A
        - Planet Patrol - I didn't know I loved you (till I saw you rock & roll), 1983; SR-23435; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
        - Planet Patrol - Danger zone, 1984; SR-23436; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23437. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # TB 846; A-side Matrix # "HOT MIX" TB-846-A
        - Planet Patrol - Danger zone, 1984; SR-23437; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23436. 2 copies. Promo
        - Planet Patrol - It wouldn't have made any difference, 1984; SR-23438; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
        - Planet Patrol - Planet Patrol, 1983; SR-23439; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23440. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # TBLP 1002; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1002-A
        - Planet Patrol - Planet Patrol, 1983; SR-23440; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23439. 2 copies. Promo
        - Planet Patrol - Planet Patrol, 1983; SR-23441; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
        - Planet Patrol - Planet Patrol, 1983; SR-23442; Planet Patrol (Box 390)
        - Planning By Numbers - 1: catch the beat, 1982; SR-23443; Planning By Numbers (Box 390)
          Catalog # BEGA 32; A-side Matrix # TAPE ONE BEGA 32 A
          Beggars Banquet
        - Plante, Josef - Luminous moodswing, 2001; SR-23444; Plante, Josef; Simply Jeff (Box 390)
          Catalog # PM-007; A-side Matrix # S-46425 PM-007 A
          Phonomental Music
          Newport Beach, California
        - Plante, Josef - Luminous moodswing, 2001; SR-23445; Plante, Josef; Simply Jeff (Box 390)
        - Plante, Josef - Luminous moodswing, 2001; SR-23446; Plante, Josef; Simply Jeff (Box 390)
        - Plastic Bertrand - Stop ou encore, 1982; SR-23447; Plastic Bertrand (Box 390)
          Catalog # SS-421; A-side Matrix # SS-421-A
          Sugarscoop
        - Plastic Ono Band - Live peace in Toronto 1969, 1969; SR-23448; Plastic Ono Band (Box 390)
          Catalog # SW-3362; A-side Matrix # SW-1-3362-Z7
          Apple Records
        - Playa - Don't stop the music, 1997; SR-23449; Playa (Box 390)
          Catalog # Def 169-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-169-1-A-REI
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Playa Poncho - Koochie kuterz, 1995; SR-23450; Playa Poncho (Box 390)
          Catalog # CAS 7529; A-side Matrix # XSS7529A-2A
          So So Def
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Playa Poncho - Whatz up, whatz up, 1995; SR-23451; Playa Poncho; L.A. Sno (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23452. 2 copies.Different jacket
          Catalog # CAS 7159; A-side Matrix # XSS7159A-1A
        - Playa Poncho - Whatz up, whatz up, 1995; SR-23452; Playa Poncho; L.A. Sno (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23451. 2 copies.Different jacket
        - Players Association - Turn the music up!; Ride the groove; Everybody dance, 1979; SR-23453; Players Association (Box 390)
          Catalog # SPV 22; A-side Matrix # SPV22A-1A
          Vanguard
        - Players Association - Turn the music up!, 1979; SR-23454; Players Association (Box 390)
          Catalog # SPV 22; A-side Matrix # SPV-SRV 22 A -2A
        - Playgirls - Our picture of a man, 1984; SR-23455; Playgirls (Box 390)
          Catalog # SUD 028; A-side Matrix # SUD-028-A
          Sutra Records
        - Pleasant - Shorty, 2000; SR-23456; Pleasant (Box 390)
          Catalog # OTR-2645; A-side Matrix # OTR-2645-A
          On the Rise Records
          Inwood, New York
        - Pleasure - Rare pleasure tracks, 2000; SR-23457; Pleasure (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23458. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LU730; A-side Matrix # LU-730-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 43635 &
          Listen Up Records & Tapes
          Maryland
        - Pleasure - Rare pleasure tracks, 2000; SR-23458; Pleasure (Box 390)
          In same jacket as # SR-23457. 2 copies.
        - Pleasure - Olly olly oxan free, 1993; SR-23459; Pleasure (Box 390)
          Catalog # SBC708-1; A-side Matrix # SBC-708-1-A DCHARLES
          Sound By Charlie Music Company
        - Pleasure - Give it up, 1982; SR-23480; Pleasure (Box 390)
          Catalog # JT-13242; A-side Matrix # PD-13242-A
        - Pleasure - Sending my love, 1982; SR-23460; Pleasure (Box 390)
          Catalog # JD-13068; A-side Matrix # PD-13068-A MR 25410
        - Pleasure Crew - So good, 1987; SR-23461; Pleasure Crew (Box 390)
          Catalog # FAC 169; A-side Matrix # FAC 169 A1 MPO
          Factory
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Pleasure Dome - I can see a day for 10 min., 1995; SR-23462; Pleasure Dome (Box 390)
          Catalog # SEX-015; A-side Matrix # SEX-015 A
          Sex Mania
        - Pleasure, Eddy - Let the little girl dance; Ring me for service, 1987; SR-23463; Pleasure, Eddy (Box 390)
          Catalog # DMD 1106; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-53040-1
        - Plez - What goes around comes around, 1986; SR-23464; Plez (Box 390)
          Catalog # MET 460; A-side Matrix # MET-460-A
        - Plonquitte, Georges - Carnaval, 1985; SR-23465; Plonquitte, Georges (Box 390)
          Catalog # LM 6012; A-side Matrix # LM 6012 A
          LM Production
        - Plump DJs - A plump night out (sampler 1), 2000; SR-23466; Plump DJs; War (Box 390)
          Catalog # FLR.021; A-side Matrix # FLR-021-A
          Finger Lickin' Records
        - Plump DJs - A plump night out (sampler 1), 2000; SR-23467; Plump DJs; War (Box 390)
        - Plump DJs - Big groovy fucker; T.B. reality, 2002; SR-23468; Plump DJs (Box 390)
          Catalog # FLR.031; A-side Matrix # FLR 31 A1
        - Plump DJs - Big groovy fucker; T.B. reality, 2002; SR-23469; Plump DJs (Box 390)
        - Plunky - Every way but loose (new re-mixed version), 1982; SR-23470; Plunky; Oneness of Juju (Box 390)
          Catalog # SUD 007; A-side Matrix # SUD-007-A
        - Plush - Free and easy, 1982; SR-23471; Plush (Box 390)
          Catalog # JT-13337; A-side Matrix # PD-13337-A-RCA-1
        - Plush - Burnin' love, 1982; SR-23472; Plush (Box 390)
          Catalog # JT-13229; A-side Matrix # PD-13229-A-6S
        - Plutonic - One life, 1992; SR-23473; Plutonic; Wilson, Mike 'Hitman' (Box 390)
          Catalog # PLUTONIC 1; A-side Matrix # PLUTONIC 1A-01-01
        - Pluuto - Isn't it crazy, 1988; SR-23474; Pluuto (Box 390)
          Catalog # ZYX 5837; A-side Matrix # ZYX 5837 A
          Techno Drome International
          Dorchheim, Germany
        - Plyers & Chaka Demus - Rough this year; One more dead, 1992; SR-23475; Plyers & Chaka Demus; Redrose, Anthony; Ranks, Fragga (Box 390)
          Catalog # SPD 252; A-side Matrix # SPD-A-252 RUFF THIS YEAR DONIAW
          Super Power
        - P.M. Dawn - Plastic, 1993; SR-23476; P.M. Dawn (Box 390)
          Catalog # 422-864 967-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 422 864 967-1-A5/HS
          Gee Street
        - P.M. Dawn - Of the heart, of the soul and of the cross: the utopian experience, 1991; SR-23477; P.M. Dawn (Box 390)
          Catalog # GEEA 7/510 276-1; A-side Matrix # GEE A7-A3
        - P.M. Dawn - Plastic, 1993; SR-23478; P.M. Dawn (Box 390)
        - P.M. Dawn - Set adrift on memory bliss, 1991; SR-23479; P.M. Dawn (Box 390)
          Catalog # 422-866 095-1; A-side Matrix # 422-866 095-1AS SP
        - P.M. Dawn - Reality used to be a friend of mine, 1991; SR-23481; P.M. Dawn (Box 391)
          Catalog # 422-866 821-1; A-side Matrix # 422-866-821-1 AS SP
        - P.M. Dawn - Sometimes I miss you so much (dedicated to the Christ consciousness), 1995; SR-23482; P.M. Dawn (Box 391)
          Catalog # 422-854 477-1; A-side Matrix # 422-854-477-1-A P
        - P.M. Dawn - Plastic, 1993; SR-23483; P.M. Dawn (Box 391)
        - P.M. Dawn - The ways of the wind, 1993; SR-23484; P.M. Dawn (Box 391)
          Catalog # 422-862 475-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 422-862-751-1-A5/HS
        - PMD - Swing your own thing; Shadé business, 1994; SR-23485; PMD (Box 391)
          Catalog # RDAB 64242-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64242-1-A
          RCA Records Label
        - PMD - Swing your own thing (remix), 1994; SR-23486; PMD (Box 391)
          Catalog # RDCD-64250-1; A-side Matrix # RDCD-64250-1-A1
        - PMD - Rugged-n-raw, 1996; SR-23487; PMD (Box 391)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0485; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0485A
          Relativity Recordings, Inc.
        - PMD - Rugged-n-raw, 1996; SR-23488; PMD (Box 391)
        - P.N.Y. - P.N.Y., 1984; SR-23489; P.N.Y. (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-23490. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 8352; A-side Matrix # 8352A
        - P.N.Y. - P.N.Y., 1984; SR-23490; P.N.Y. (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-23489. 2 copies.
        - Po' Rich - Rap iz gonna get hurt, 1997; SR-23491; Po' Rich (Box 391)
          Catalog # NPE 1423-1; A-side Matrix # PA 197 NPE-1423-1A
          Next Plateau Entertainment
        - Pockets - Take it on up, 1978; SR-23492; Pockets (Box 391)
          Catalog # ASD 483; A-side Matrix # XSS 164412-1B
        - Poetry - Everything I do, 1989; SR-23493; Poetry (Box 391)
          Catalog # PW 447; A-side Matrix # PW-447-A 1-2
        - Poets of Rhythm - Discern; Define (Disc One), 2001; SR-23494; Poets of Rhythm (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-23495
          Catalog # QP 023-1; A-side Matrix # QP23-1A
          Quannum Projects
        - Poets of Rhythm - Discern; Define (Disc Two), 2001; SR-23495; Poets of Rhythm (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-23494
          Catalog # QP 023-1; A-side Matrix # QP23-1C
        - Poindexter, Buster - Cannibal; Hot hot hot (summer of '88 mix), 1988; SR-13555; Poindexter, Buster (Box 391)
          Catalog # 8708-1-RDA1; A-side Matrix # 8708-1-RDA1-A
        - Poindexter, Buster - Hot hot hot, 1987; SR-23496; Poindexter, Buster; Banshees of Blue (Box 391)
          Catalog # 6737-1-RDAB; A-side Matrix # 6737-1-RD-A
        - Poindexter, Buster - International playboy, 1990; SR-23497; Poindexter, Buster (Box 391)
          Catalog # 2531-1-RDBA; A-side Matrix # 2531-1-RDA
        - Point Blank MC's - What the party needs, 1986; SR-23498; Point Blank MC's (Box 391)
          Catalog # BAB 105; A-side Matrix # BAB-105-A
          Beauty and the Beat Records
          Elizabeth, New Jersey
        - Point Of View - Are you ready? (for the funk), 1981; SR-23499; Point Of View (Box 391)
          Catalog # PRS 9781; A-side Matrix # PRS-9781-A
          Pointsouth Records
          Greenville, South Carolina
        - Pointer, Bonnie - Heaven must have sent you, 1978; SR-23500; Pointer, Bonnie (Box 391)
          Catalog # M 00020 D1; A-side Matrix # M00020D1-65087-D-B-18A
        - Pointer, Noel - Direct hit, 1982; SR-28000; Pointer, Noel (Box 391)
          Catalog # SP-219; A-side Matrix # SP-1-219-P-1
          Liberty
        - Pointer, Noel - Living for the city, 1977; SR-28001; Pointer, Noel (Box 391)
          Catalog # SP-147; A-side Matrix # SP-147-M
          Blue Note
        - Pointer, Noel - Hold on, 1978; SR-28002; Pointer, Noel (Box 391)
          Catalog # UA-LA848-H; A-side Matrix # UALA-848-1
          United Artists Records
        - Pointer Sisters - I need you, 1982; SR-28003; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # JR-13632; A-side Matrix # JR-13632-A-2
          Planet Records
        - Pointer Sisters - Jump (for my love), 1983; SR-28004; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # JW-13781; A-side Matrix # JW-13781-A-105
        - Pointer Sisters - He's so shy, 1980; SR-28005; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # AS-11459; A-side Matrix # ASS-11459-A-SP SP
        - Pointer Sisters - Black & white, 1981; SR-28006; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # AYL1-5092; A-side Matrix # AYL1-5092-A-15
        - Pointer Sisters - Pointer Sisters' greatest hits, 1982; SR-28007; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # 60203; A-side Matrix # SM1-1 60203-A-4-SH-SP 2504 SLM
        - Pointer Sisters - Automatic, 1983; SR-28008; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28009. Different discs.
          Catalog # YD-13721; A-side Matrix # YD-13721-A-5S
        - Pointer Sisters - Automatic, 1983; SR-28009; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28008. Different discs.
          Catalog # JD-13721; A-side Matrix # YD-13721-A-5S
        - Pointer Sisters - Automatic, 1983; SR-28010; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
        - Pointer Sisters - I'm so excited, 1982; SR-28011; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # JD-13325; A-side Matrix # JD-13325-A-1
        - Pointer Sisters - The Pointer Sisters, 1973; SR-28012; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # BTS 48; A-side Matrix # BTS 48 6027-1C T
          Blue Thumb Records
        - Pointer Sisters - The Pointer Sisters live at the Opera House (Disc one), 1974; SR-28013; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28014. Double album.
          Catalog # BTS 8002; A-side Matrix # BTS 8002 6093-1D T
        - Pointer Sisters - The Pointer Sisters live at the Opera House (Disc two), 1974; SR-28014; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28013. Double album.
          Catalog # BTS 8002; A-side Matrix # BTS 8002 6094-1D T
        - Pointer Sisters - Friend's advice (don't take it), 1990; SR-28015; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28016. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # L33-17922; A-side Matrix # MOT-9991-B6-4
        - Pointer Sisters - Friend's advice (don't take it), 1990; SR-28016; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28015. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # MOT-4661; A-side Matrix # MOT-9991-B6-5
        - Pointer Sisters - I'm so excited, 1982; SR-28017; Pointer Sisters (Box 391)
          Catalog # JR-13858; A-side Matrix # JR-13858-A-DS
        - Poison - Cosmic dancing, 2005; SR-28018; Poison (Box 391)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0070; A-side Matrix # DEL LP 0070 A
          Funky Delicacies
        - Poison Clan - Fire up this funk, 1995; SR-28019; Poison Clan; Rufftown Mob (Box 391)
          Catalog # 9521; A-side Matrix # S-31745 SIDE A
          Represent Entertainment
        - Poison Clan - Fire up this funk, 1995; SR-28020; Poison Clan; Rufftown Mob (Box 391)
        - Poison Clan - Action, 1992; SR-28021; Poison Clan (Box 391)
          Catalog # PR-229-1; A-side Matrix # E-732-A
          Luke Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Poison Clan - Fire up this funk, 1995; SR-28022; Poison Clan; Rufftown Mob (Box 391)
          Catalog # WAR 185-DJ; A-side Matrix # WAR-185-A
          Warlock Records
        - Poison Ivy - Feel how I feel, 1986; SR-28023; Poison Ivy (Box 391)
          Catalog # TH-108; A-side Matrix # TH-108-A
          Top Hits
          Hialeah Gardens, Florida
        - Poison Pen - I'm fuckin' you up; Inner city hoodlum, 2004; SR-28024; Poison Pen (Box 391)
          Catalog # NE 20542; A-side Matrix # NE-20542-A
          Nervous Records
        - Polecats - John I'm only dancing, 1981; SR-28025; Polecats (Box 391)
          Catalog # POLE 10; A-side Matrix # tone POLECATS JOHN1
        - Police - I burn for you; Only you, 1982; SR-28026; Police; Sting (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28027. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # SP-17216; A-side Matrix # T1 AIM SP017216A-T2
          A&M Records
        - Police - I burn for you; Only you, 1982; SR-28027; Police; Sting (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28026. 2 copies.
        - Police - Reggatta de blanc, 1979; SR-28028; Police (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28029. Different discs.
          Catalog # AMLH 64792; A-side Matrix # AMLH-64792-A-5
        - Police - Reggatta de blanc, 1979; SR-28029; Police (Box 391)
          In same jacket as # SR-28028. Different discs.
          Catalog # AMLH 64792; A-side Matrix # AMLH-64792-A6
        - Police - Synchronicity, 1983; SR-28030; Police (Box 391)
          Catalog # SP-3735; A-side Matrix # SP-03735A-1D
        - Police - Don't stand so close to me '86, 1986; SR-28031; Police (Box 391)
          Catalog # SP-12207; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012207-A ES -1
        - Police - Every breath you take (the singles), 1986; SR-28032; Police (Box 391)
          Catalog # SP-03902; A-side Matrix # SP-03902-A ES-1
        - Politicians - The Politicians (featuring McKinley Jackson), 1972; SR-28033; Politicians; Jackson, McKinley (Box 391)
          Catalog # HA 711; A-side Matrix # K-5240
          Hot Wax
        - Polly Famous - Top baller; Phantom of the Opera; Heat; Opera hall mix, 1996; SR-28034; Polly Famous; Stallion; Mad Lion (Box 391)
          Catalog # SC-9901; A-side Matrix # SC-9901-C
          Spinnas
        - Polyrock - Above the fruited Plain, 1982; SR-28035; Polyrock (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28036. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PVC 6901; A-side Matrix # PVC 6901 A
          PVC Records
          South Plainfield, New Jersey
        - Polyrock - Above the fruited Plain, 1982; SR-28036; Polyrock (Box 392)
          In same jacket as # SR-28035. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Polyrock - RCA special radio series volume xiv, 1981; SR-28037; Polyrock (Box 392)
          Catalog # DJL1-4183; A-side Matrix # DJL1-4183A-1
          Pinebrook, New Jersey
        - Pompey, Ron - Beyond, 1987; SR-28038; Pompey, Ron (Box 392)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # NC 0008 A
          Hibiscus Records
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Ponce, Machito - Plastico (the Lucci-n-Cruz remixes), 1997; SR-28039; Ponce, Machito (Box 392)
          Catalog # 2324-1RLDJ; A-side Matrix # BMG-Ariola 2324-1RLDJ-A
          Ariola Dance
          Coral Gables, Florida
        - Ponsar, Serge - Out in the night, 1983; SR-28040; Ponsar, Serge (Box 392)
          Catalog # 0-20124; A-side Matrix # 0-20124-A-SH1 B-18148-SH1 SLM 4515
        - Pool - Dance it down, 1983; SR-28041; Pool (Box 392)
          Catalog # PDM-831; A-side Matrix # S-10272- PDM-83-1-A
          Moment Productions
          Austin, Texas